questions=[
				{
					"id":1,
					"qType":"mChoice", 
					"question":"What is the name of IBM's supercomputer powered Humanioid Robot?",
					"option1":"Pepper",
					"option2":"Peppa",
					"option3":"Walto",
					"option4":"Walter",
					"answer":"Pepper"
				},
				{
					"id":2,
					"qType":"mChoice", 
					"question":"who is the founder of IBM?",
					"option1":"Thomas J.Watson",
					"option2":"Frank T.Cary",
					"option3":"David Duffield",
					"option4":"Charles Flint",
					"answer":"Charles Flint"
				},
				
				{
					"id":3,
					"qType":"mChoice", 
					"question":"what is the speed of T3 line in mbps?",
					"option1":"1.5",
					"option2":"4.5",
					"option3":"15",
					"option4":"45",
					"answer":"45"
				},
				{
					"id":4,
					"qType":"mChoice", 
					"question":"How many /30 blocks can be obtained from a /24 IP block?",
					"option1":"30",
					"option2":"32",
					"option3":"16",
					"option4":"64",
					"answer":"64"
				},
				{
					"id":5,
					"qType":"noChoice", 
					"question":" It goes all over the world, but always stays in a corner. What is that??",
					"answer":"Stamp",
					"points":0,
					"passPoints":0,
					"allowPass":false
				},
				{
					"id":6,
					"qType":"noChoice", 
					"question":" I'm the most slippery country in the world. Tell who am I??",
					"answer":"Greece",
					"points":0,
					"passPoints":0,
					"allowPass":false
				},
				{
					"id":7,
					"qType":"mChoice", 
					"question":"Who is the CEO and President of AT&T?",
					"option1":"John Donovan",
					"option2":"Randall L. Stephenson",
					"option3":"John Stankey",
					"option4":"John J. Stephens",
					"answer":"Randall L. Stephenson"
				},
				{
					"id":8,
					"qType":"mChoice", 
					"question":"Where is AT&T head quarters located(City Name)?",
					"option1":"San Antonio, Texas",
					"option2":"Houstan, Texas",
					"option3":"Austin, Texas",
					"option4":"Dallas, Texas",
					"answer":"Dallas, Texas"
				},
				{
					"id":9,
					"qType":"mChoice", 
					"question":"which configlet type removes the line 'no shutdown' from the interface(in 	LPP)?",
					"option1":"IPC",
					"option2":"IBC",
					"option3":"TTU",
					"option4":"RC",
					"answer":"TTU"
				},
				{
					"id":10,
					"qType":"mChoice", 
					"question":"Expand ICORE?",
					"option1":"Internet Common Operations Resource and Engineering",
					"option2":"Interspan Common Operations Resource and Engineering",
					"option3":"Interactive Common Operations Resource and Engineering",
					"option4":"Interops Common Operations Resource and Engineering ",
					"answer":"Interspan Common Operations Resource and Engineering"
				},
				{
					"id":11,
					"qType":"noChoice", 
					"question":"In an empty land a man was found dead wearing his back pack, How could have he died?",
					"answer":"His Parachute failed to open",
					"points":0,
					"passPoints":0,
					"allowPass":false
				},
				{
					"id":12,
					"qType":"noChoice", 
					"question":"A man went to a party and drank some of the punch. He then left early. Everyone at the party who drunk the punch subsequently died of poisioning. Why did the man not die?",
					"answer":"Poison came from the ice cubes.",
					"points":0,
					"passPoints":0,
					"allowPass":false
				},
				{
					"id":13,
					"qType":"mChoice", 
					"question":"In 1924 IBM was renamed from the orginal name which was founded in 1911,what was the original name?" ,
					"option1":"Computing-Transporting-Reviewing Company",
					"option2":"Computing-Tabulating-Reviewing Company",
					"option3":"Computing-Tabulating-Recording Company",
					"option4":"Computing-Transporting-Recording Company",
					"answer":"Computing-Tabulating-Recording Company"
				},
				{
					"id":14,
					"qType":"mChoice", 
					"question":"What is the name of IBM's supercomputer that won the chess match against a world chess champion in 1997?" ,
					"option1":"Big Blue",
					"option2":"Deep Blue",
					"option3":"Blue Queen",
					"option4":"Blue Fish",
					"answer":"Deep Blue"
				},
			];

points={"points":10,"delayedPoints":5,"passPoints":2};
allowPass = true;
delayChoice=true;
